# JENNIFER WU

UNIVERSITY OF WATERLOO

Computer Science with Computational Fine Art Option







github.com/JWKaiqi 📈 k43wu0826@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

I am software developer with experience in mobile, web, and desktop applications. I am passionate about computational fine art, graphics and digital art. Some other fun facts about me: I like cooking and baking. I love my dog Coco and my obese cat Momo.

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Science with Computational Fine Art Option, Co-operative Program, University of Waterloo, Canada Sep 2013 - Apr 2018

## SKILLS

- Languages: Java, C++, C, C#, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Lua, Bash
- Mobile: Swift, Objective-C, Android
- Frameworks: OpenGL, WebGL, Qt, Processing, Angular, ASP.Net
- Tools: Git, Photoshop, Premiere, Illustrator, Maya

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Palette Gear. Software Developer

SEP 2017 - DEC 2017

- Took part in developing the desktop application for their modular hardware controllers.
- Worked primarily on Adobe SDK development, WebGL 3D modeling, Qt and QML application development.
- Fixed many of the company's backlog bugs.

#### Ontario Institute for Cancer Research. Software Developer

MAY 2017 - SEP 2017

- Front-end Angular / AngularJS development
- Integrated Elastic search engine into the product search page
- Used tools and languages such as Docker, Quay.io, CWL. WDL and etc.

#### Bell and Howell, Software Developer

JAN 2016 - MAY 2016

- Developed and updated multiple application by using ASP.NET, C#, VB, MySQL, and XML
- Updated and maintained the company's backend support

#### PROJECT

- Computer Graphic: Raytracer; Barcraft 3D Sandbox; 3D humanoid puppet, Geometric pipeline.
- Mobile: I-Love-Takeout (IOS): Rise of Numericons (Android)
- Website: Dream Cabinet; Spotify Managemer; Personal website
- Desktop App: Entity Relationship Diagram Editor, Tetris Game